Welcome To Mexico
The Shepherd: Border Patrol is a action, crime,
thriller film directed by Isaac Florentine.
A Texas cop battles ex-navy seals who are trying to
traffic drugs from Mexico into the USA.
Jack Robideaux, played by Jean-Claude Van Damme.
Kassie Robideaux, played by Bianca Bree.
Jed, played by Phil McKee.
Karp, played by Scott Adkins.
Arthur Pennigton, played by Miles Anderson.
Wray, played by Todd Jensen.
The Shepherd: Border Patrol (also known simply as The Shepherd) is a
2008 American action film directed by Isaac Florentine.
It stars Jean-Claude Van Damme, with a supporting cast of Natalie J.
Robb, Stephen Lord, Gary McDonald, Scott Adkins and Van
Damme's real life daughter Bianca Van Varenberg.
The film was released on direct-to-DVD in the United States on March 4, 2008.
The film explores themes of small town, martial arts,
kidnapping, drug trafficking, illegal immigration.
The tone is intense.